so here's some things that you might have missed the trump administration did another extrajudicial
killing in the waters off venezuela taking the lives of four men that they claim are narco
whateverists it's a claim they have absolutely no idea nonetheless uh the right-wing party in
venezuela is teaming up to work with the trump administration in what we can only expect is a
attempted coup to turn venezuela into an ally a right-wing ally of the trump administration
that is happening in real time right the first wave of deportees from the global summit flotilla
have been sent home they prevented us from having medicine for those who needed medicine they only
gave us water after 32 hours we had barely any food we were um woken up at three in the morning with
dogs and um snipers walking into our room waking us up every two hours to prevent us from sleeping
however there are still many more there particularly u.s citizens and california's
avac um congress people senator alex padilla and adam schiff have said nothing nothing even
though constituents of theirs are imprisoned in israel yep another summit flotilla from turkey
has uh set sail as well as a boat that was actually attacked earlier this year uh but it is back in
the water and they're going with supplies medical supplies um food aid etc so the continual effort to
break the gaza siege via the water is moving forward now in response to the global summit flotilla
being blocked you have italy that has shut down everything for two weeks i would think that
every single news outlet in the u.s would be reporting that an entire country has been shut down
by the way they have a fascist woman in power so it's not like that has to be the reason why people
don't move people gonna move when the people want to move speaking of shutting things down what is not
also something also not being reported is that a bunch of jewish people and christians rabbi and clergy
got on the brooklyn bridge and shut that down in new york and were arrested in addition to that
you had a bunch of anti-zionist israelis that really physically tried to break the siege in israel
and uh they were also arrested and attacked in today's water is wet news trey reed the young man
who was found hanging from a tree in mississippi his autopsy came back they found evidence of blunt
force trauma to the back of his head and it has been proven by this examiner that not only was he
strangled preemptively before hanging from the tree but now there's been investigations that show that
he was having an online conflict with some white boys that go to that school a few days prior there
have been uprisings all over the world madagascar morocco nepal indonesia and something that's been
uniquely attached to all of them is this idea that they're gen z uprisings and whenever i see a
pattern in reporting i'm always going to have a bell go off because patterns and reporting are
typically an example of propaganda so we have to look a bit further into what these uprisings are
really about and why they are attributing all of them to quote unquote gen z when the truth and the
reality is we add peru to that we add argentina to that that we add france to that that all of these
uprisings are related to corruption and it's not simply gen z that's tired of corruption so i think
that there's a attempt right here to try and paint gen z as some sort of rabble rousers uh and it
wouldn't surprise me also if they didn't realize that painting them as rabble rousers is actually
a positive paintbrush but that's another story for another time please check out my interview with
mark wayne from colonial outcast podcast on youtube amanda seals tv he gives a great explanation
of ways in which you can actively build community to challenge what is happening like literally step
by step and i think it's worth everybody to go and listen to that who finds himself saying what do we
do he's got a plan for you in order for us to effectively um change this world we're going to have
to change ourselves we're going to have to change how we relate to each other as human beings and i think
that part of that is uh creating a humanistic style of interchanging uh of really being concerned about
other people who are struggling with us i think another part of that is creating a sense of community
in the united states what exists right now is total alienation people are alienated from each other to the
point where people are afraid to have eye contact with other people afraid to smile at people afraid
to say good morning good afternoon how you're doing that is hell
thank you
do
and